/*-------------------------------Questions for Pro Level-------------------------*/
/*-------------------------------------------------------------------------------*/
window.gameProLevelQuestions = [
    {
        question: "21.42% of 182 is what % of 390?",
        answerArray: ["20", "10", "30", "15"],
        matchedValue: "10",
        correctAnswer: "10",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "The % increase from 30 to 80 is?",
        answerArray: ["60%", "150%", "160%", "166.66%"],
        matchedValue: "166.66%",
        correctAnswer: "166.66%",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "What % of 30 is 50?",
        answerArray: ["12", "20", "15", "16"],
        matchedValue: "15",
        correctAnswer: "15",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "The average of 40, 60 and 180 is?",
        answerArray: ["70", "60", "40", "100"],
        matchedValue: "60",
        correctAnswer: "60",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "The number of distinct factors of 32 is",
        answerArray: ["6", "8", "7", "10"],
        matchedValue: "6",
        correctAnswer: "6",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "The remainder when 102400088 is divided by 2 is?",
        answerArray: ["1", "2", "4", "0"],
        matchedValue: "0",
        correctAnswer: "0",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "The greatest prime number less than 16 is?",
        answerArray: ["7", "15", "13", "11"],
        matchedValue: "13",
        correctAnswer: "13",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following has most number of divisors?",
        answerArray: ["99", "101", "176", "182"],
        matchedValue: "176",
        correctAnswer: "176",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "The H.C.F of 3556 and 3444 is?",
        answerArray: ["0.03", "0.9", "0.18", "0.108"],
        matchedValue: "0.18",
        correctAnswer: "0.18",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "The G.C.D of 1.08, 0.36 and 0.9 is?",
        answerArray: ["31", "40", "50", "30"],
        matchedValue: "30",
        correctAnswer: "30",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "What is 394 times 113?",
        answerArray: ["44402", "44522", "44632", "44802"],
        matchedValue: "44522",
        correctAnswer: "44522",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "1260 / 14 / 9 = ?",
        answerArray: ["9", "10", "81", "810"],
        matchedValue: "810",
        correctAnswer: "810",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "2056 * 987 = ?",
        answerArray: ["1936372", "2029272", "1896172", "1923472"],
        matchedValue: "2029272",
        correctAnswer: "2029272",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "The smallest 3 digit prime number is?",
        answerArray: ["999", "111", "100", "101"],
        matchedValue: "101",
        correctAnswer: "101",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "? is the smallest prime number.",
        answerArray: ["1", "0", "2", "3"],
        matchedValue: "2",
        correctAnswer: "2",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "2 - 2 + 2 - 2 +.......101 terms = ?",
        answerArray: ["-2", "0", "2", "1"],
        matchedValue: "2",
        correctAnswer: "2",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "What is 230% of 15% of 400?",
        answerArray: ["138", "130", "200", "136"],
        matchedValue: "138",
        correctAnswer: "138[",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "7% of 9 is what % of 7?",
        answerArray: ["7", "10", "0.9", "9"],
        matchedValue: "9",
        correctAnswer: "9",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "The number of distinct factors of 10 are?",
        answerArray: ["6", "10", "2", "4"],
        matchedValue: "4",
        correctAnswer: "4",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "The least common multiple of 22 and 6 is?",
        answerArray: ["68", "44", "22", "66"],
        matchedValue: "66",
        correctAnswer: "66",
        isVisited: 0
    }
];
